donnahay.com.au 2019-03-02

# Privacy Policy | Donna Hay

In this privacy policy “donna hay” means donna hay general store pty ltd ACN 135 066 554 as trustee for the donna hay general store trust ABN 62 892 484 639 and all references to “donna hay” include its related bodies corporate. The words “you” and “your” mean the person or entity contacting the “donna hay” website for any purpose.

######  **protecting your information is  important**

At “donna hay” we understand the importance you attach to information that identifies you (your ‘personal information’). This privacy policy tells you how we collect information when you visit this website and what we do with it. 

###### **what information we collect about you + what we do with it  **

“donna hay” collects information about you each time you come to any part of the “donna hay” website. We collect information about the time, date, duration and usage of the “donna hay” website. We collect personal information for the purpose of providing a specific product or service requested by our customers and consumer marketing data. Certain information may be required in order to provide this product or service, including your full name, e-mail address, billing address, contact phone numbers and credit card number. “donna hay” uses statistics about the use of our website to continually improve it and to improve our customer service. If you submit information to “donna hay” through the “donna hay” website either using an electronic form or by sending an email we collect that information and use it for the purposes that you have provided it. We also collect information when people join our mailing list at the donna hay general store. As with all information we hold this will be compliant with our privacy policy. In addition, we may use your information to provide you with special offers, information about new products and special promotions that we think may interest you. If you do not want to receive this information, you can let us know by sending “donna hay” an email at  **[enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au](mailto:enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au)** , or by mail to “donna hay” Level 5, 83-97 Kippax St, Surry Hills NSW 2010 or call (02) 9282 6500. Please provide us with your customer details including name, address and contact number. In addition, indicate if you do not wish to receive any more promotional material. The information collected may also be used to inform you of additional products and services, which may be of interest to you. All marketing material sent to you will include an option for you to request removal from our contact lists for any future marketing.

###### **what is a cookie and what are they used for?  **

A cookie is a text file placed into the memory of your computer by “donna hay” computers and “donna hay” can retrieve a copy of this text file. Cookies are used for a number of purposes. “donna hay” uses cookies to identify you for the purposes of monitoring use and aiding security in your use of the website. The cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information to identify you or your email address. You have the option of setting your web browser to reject cookies, which may impact negatively on your experience of this website. We rely on the accuracy of the information you provide to us. If you think that we hold information about you that is incorrect in any way, or out of date, or you simply want to notify us of something new, please send “donna hay” an email at **[enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au](mailto:enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au)** indicating that your information is incorrect and the new details.

###### **our security procedures  **

In designing this website, “donna hay” has incorporated security procedures and practices that “donna hay” considers are consistent with Australian industry practice. “donna hay” reviews its security procedures from time to time and updates them when relevant. Personal information about you and your business with “donna hay” is only accessible by you and by those who are authorised by us to access it, for approved business purposes.

###### **links to other sites  **

You may be able to access various other sites by clicking on links that “donna hay” has provided. You should be aware that other sites may not be subject to the “donna hay” privacy standards and procedures.   

###### **changes to our privacy policy  **

This information relates to “donna hay” current privacy standards. “donna hay” may vary our privacy standards from time to time. We will notify you of these changes by publishing them on this website. “donna hay” is committed to protecting the personal privacy of our customers, and observes the Australian Privacy Principles pursuant to the Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988 (as amended from time to time).

###### **use of information outside Australia  **

As part of your contract with us, “donna hay” may need to transfer some of your personal information to one of “donna hay” international affiliates. “donna hay” will use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the recipient jurisdiction has in place a similar regime which recognises your right to privacy. All “donna hay” international affiliates have privacy statements which comply with the legal requirements of their jurisdiction.

###### **feedback  **

If you have any comments or suggestions regarding the “donna hay” website or this privacy policy please email us at  **[enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au.](mailto:enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au)**

###### **complaints  **

If you are unhappy with any aspect of the way your personal information has been collected or handled by “donna hay”, please do not hesitate to contact us at  **[enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au.](mailto:enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au)**

Please let us know if you have any queries in relation to any aspects of the above privacy policy at  **[enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au.](mailto:enquiries@donnahaygeneralstore.com.au)**

###### **inconsistency with privacy laws**

To the extent that any of the terms of this privacy policy are deemed or held by a competent authority to be inconsistent with applicable privacy laws, such terms shall be construed or amended so as to make them consistent with applicable privacy laws.
